nine hundred and fifty reais in the account
a business idea and the one in hand
if it doesn't work out
we go on this
yesterday i created a great idea of assembling
my brownie brand
guys started to fill me with a lot of comments
saying i can have problem
if i don't register this soon
man caraca
then I'll call an expert to find out
which way to go right uncle
life asks you but the
1 day I got there
you are going to make 1 video call for me
it gets even better
and there Dani
wanted
to guide me a little more about it
first
super important
you already worry about it from the start
and I always say that the moment
sure to register a trademark
is when you got the idea of the name
you are starting right
it might work out because of the brownie
that's a pun over there
no one in Brazil will be able to have the same brand
similar to your
in the same branch of activity
so this record is super important
I just made a very difficult decision
but i think it'll be important man
I'm on that the battle will be too big
I just registered my brand
o is n p
i which is the right trademark registration
but what matters is that the first step has been taken
is on
now i'm here thinking about how to continue this thing
with only
70real in the account bro